[{"answer": "They're 100 percent innocent.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "And was the truth a victim, too?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "Pretty much.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "She was the only person you saw?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "There was a television, no cable anything like that.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Did you have a television?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "It's a concrete slab along the back of the wall.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "What was the bed like?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "CHOLS: No.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "A computer?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Just what I would see on, like, the major network television stations.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Were you following them?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "As often as you do it yourself in your cell.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "How often were you allowed to exercise?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "When did you see daylight?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "For almost 10 years, yes.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "In 10 years?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "The only thing -- the only thing you can do and maintain your sanity is to not think about the case and not think about what's happening to you.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "I mean, this is -- for an innocent man, as many believe that you are and you've always protested this -- what are you thinking when you're stuck in there?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "My health -- there's almost no medical care, no dental care, and things like that in prison so my health was deteriorating very rapidly.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What effect did it have on your health?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "It was like having a spotlight turned right in your face.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Yes, but that first moment you came out, what was it like to have daylight again?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "They don't give you forks in there.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "With your hands.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "How do you eat?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Almost immediately, and it wasn't just because of this.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "When is the first time that you hear you are going to be in trouble with this?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "The most trouble I had ever gotten into was like running away from home as a teenager, something like that.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Or were you just a bit different?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Ever broken the law?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "You were into, like, heavy metal?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Just immediately, as soon as it happened, people said a murder this horrific couldn't have just happened.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "So what happened?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "They showed up at my door the day after the bodies were found.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "When was the moment you realized you were going to be pulled in by the police?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "There's no words to even describe it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "And how did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, whenever they called him in for questioning, like you said, he was mentally retarded.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Not very well.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "How well did you know him?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "It's hard to say.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Why did you think he was doing this?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "It's hard to say.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "When is the worst moment for you?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "The evidence against us was our personal preferences in music.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What was the evidence against you, other than the word of Jessie, who we already established had a mental age of somewhere between a 5 and 8- year-olds?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, at the time they had evidence and stuff but since it didn't match us it wasn't brought up and then --", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "There's no DNA evidence against you?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "That was it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Was there anything else other than music you listened to, books you read, clothes you wore or haircuts?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "And they would attack you?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "The first few years, a lot.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "How often?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I mean I've got shattered skull, broken collarbone, teeth knocked out, multiple scars on my face and stuff from it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "I mean were you going through the same thing?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I think I fell in love with Lorri pretty much from the very first letter.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "You write about -- what are you thinking when these letters arrive?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Because I can -- I just knew this was someone unlike anyone I had ever known in my life.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Well, fortunately, for most of my life I've been a pretty grounded, responsible person so I mean I think if I had been a little more erratic in my life, then maybe -- but it was astounding because my close friends stuck by me.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "But you must have still had family, friends, and people around you, presumably, as this relationship developed, thinking, what are you doing?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I never entertained the thought of it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "How -- you know, how do you deal with that psychologically?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, on both deals, like they came to me with plea agreements, like, when I first got arrested.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "But if you didn't take this deal, he would have been facing the death penalty still, right?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "I only ever had one.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "How many execution dates did you face?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I thought there was a good possibility, just because -- you know, we were convicted of something we didn't do with no evidence.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "And in the build-up to that, did you genuinely think that you were going to get killed?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "It varies.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "How many people were on Death Row with you?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "None of mine.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Any of them believe you may be guilty?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, the thing about that is I was with my family at the time the murders occurred.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "None of yours?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Jason, why do you think Jessie was doing this?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "The closest thing I can come to explain that in my mind is like the schoolyard bully who gets the kid to cry uncle under duress.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Because if he hadn't, I don't think any of you would have gone to prison, would you?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Do you blame him?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "He's a victim as well, you think?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "You just have to keep moving forward.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "How do you deal with that psychologically?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "We were terrified for his safety, you know, when we first heard of the murders.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Was it, yes?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "CHOLS: Absolutely.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Does a part of you understand why some of their family felt they had closure with your convictions?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I can understand it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "And they just can't deal with the fact that it may not be what they had been told it was?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I knew everybody just had it wrong.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "When you saw him described as this evil ring leader of mass murder, what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Did either of you ever have suicidal thoughts?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "But not after you were put in prison?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Yeah, I did.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Did you ever try to take your own life?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I took an overdose of basically sleeping pills, anti- depressants, just because it was -- like you said a while ago, there's no light at the end of the tunnel.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "It's hard to describe.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "That moment when you walk free, how did that feel?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Lorri, were you surprised at the strength of Damien through this?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Not very often of course.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Did you see him at all during the time you were inside?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "How does he deal with what's happened to his father?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I didn't give it much thought.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Did you believe in it before this?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I would stop it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I am -- I sleep very well.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What are the practical realities of your life now?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Had your first beer yet?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I think, at one point, I went to a coffee shop and they were like what kind of coffee do you want.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Quite a few I should say, right?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I think one of the most remarkable moments that let me know that it was really finally over is we had friend who took us to see like an improv comedy routine.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What's it been like for you, Damien?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "And that was the fear you lived with for ten years?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Have you managed to get work?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "A month -- a month and a week.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "You've only been out, what, six weeks?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "The governor.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Who decides that, the governor?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Governor of Arkansas?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "I don't think it's been put together yet, but everybody's been talking about it.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Is there a petition to him at the moment?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "To the prosecutors, it's closed.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Is the case still open or was it closed?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Should it be reopened?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "In that sense, that's what we have been working on all these years with the legal team and people who have helped us.", "docId": "110929pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "That's when everybody -- right?", "qSentId": 654}]